<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>admin on IDEAS Lab</title>
    <link>/authors/admin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in admin on IDEAS Lab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/authors/admin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>New paper: Occupancy data at different spatial resolutions: Building energy performance and model calibration</title>
      <link>/post/chong-2021-occupancy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/chong-2021-occupancy/</guid>
      <description>We have a new paper:
 Adrian Chong, Godfried Augenbroe and Da Yan (2021). Occupancy data at different spatial resolutions: Building energy performance and model calibration. Applied Energy. https://doi.org/10.1016/j.apenergy.2021.116492 
 Occupancy is a significant area of interest within the field of building performance simulation. Through Bayesian calibration, the present study investigates the impact of the availability of different spatial resolution of occupancy data on the gap between predicted and measured energy use in buildings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eplusr: A framework for integrating building energy simulation and data-driven analytics</title>
      <link>/publication/jia-2020-eplusr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/jia-2020-eplusr/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/author/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/author/admin/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Adrian Chong is an Assistant Professor in the Department of the Built Environment at the National University of Singapore (NUS). His research interest is in building energy modeling and simulation, focusing on model calibration and uncertainty quantification. At NUS, he leads the Integrated Data, Energy Analysis + Simulation (IDEAS) lab, a multidisciplinary group researching the interaction between building performance simulation, measured data, and machine learning. Adrian is also the subject editor (validation, calibration, and uncertainty) for the journal Building Simulation and an NUS principal investigator at the SinBerBEST program Theme E - Cyber-Physical Testbed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>