<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>admin on IDEAS Lab</title>
    <link>/authors/admin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in admin on IDEAS Lab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/authors/admin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Calibrating building energy simulation models: A review of the basics to guide future work</title>
      <link>/publication/chong-2021-calibrating/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/chong-2021-calibrating/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantifying the effectiveness of desk dividers in reducing droplet and airborne virus transmission</title>
      <link>/publication/li-2021-quantifying/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/li-2021-quantifying/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building occupancy forecasting: A systematical and critical review</title>
      <link>/publication/jin-2021-building/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/jin-2021-building/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forecasting building occupancy: A temporal-sequential analysis and machine learning integrated approach</title>
      <link>/publication/jin-2021-forecasting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/jin-2021-forecasting/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eplusr: A framework for integrating building energy simulation and data-driven analytics</title>
      <link>/publication/jia-2020-eplusr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/jia-2020-eplusr/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/author/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/author/admin/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Adrian Chong is an Assistant Professor in the Department of the Built Environment at the National University of Singapore (NUS). His research interest is in building energy modeling and simulation, focusing on model calibration and uncertainty quantification. At NUS, he leads the Integrated Data, Energy Analysis + Simulation (IDEAS) lab, a multidisciplinary group researching the interaction between building performance simulation, measured data, and machine learning. Adrian is also the subject editor (validation, calibration, and uncertainty) for the journal Building Simulation and an NUS principal investigator at the SinBerBEST program Theme E - Cyber-Physical Testbed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>