<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>IDEAS Lab</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on IDEAS Lab</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2030 13:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	    <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Example Talk</title>
      <link>/talk/example/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2030 13:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/example/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click on the &lt;strong&gt;Slides&lt;/strong&gt; button above to view the built-in slides feature.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Slides can be added in a few ways:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create&lt;/strong&gt; slides using Academic&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/managing-content/#create-slides&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Slides&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; feature and link using &lt;code&gt;slides&lt;/code&gt; parameter in the front matter of the talk file&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Upload&lt;/strong&gt; an existing slide deck to &lt;code&gt;static/&lt;/code&gt; and link using &lt;code&gt;url_slides&lt;/code&gt; parameter in the front matter of the talk file&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Embed&lt;/strong&gt; your slides (e.g. Google Slides) or presentation video on this page using &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/writing-markdown-latex/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;shortcodes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further talk details can easily be added to this page using &lt;em&gt;Markdown&lt;/em&gt; and $\rm \LaTeX$ math code.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal thermal comfort models using digital twins: Preference prediction with BIM-extracted spatial–temporal proximity data from Build2Vec</title>
      <link>/publication/abdelrahman-2022-personal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/abdelrahman-2022-personal/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calibrating building energy simulation models: A review of the basics to guide future work</title>
      <link>/publication/chong-2021-calibrating/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/chong-2021-calibrating/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantifying the effectiveness of desk dividers in reducing droplet and airborne virus transmission</title>
      <link>/publication/li-2021-quantifying/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/li-2021-quantifying/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building occupancy forecasting: A systematical and critical review</title>
      <link>/publication/jin-2021-building/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/jin-2021-building/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forecasting building occupancy: A temporal-sequential analysis and machine learning integrated approach</title>
      <link>/publication/jin-2021-forecasting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/jin-2021-forecasting/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impact of occupant related data on identification and model predictive control for buildings</title>
      <link>/publication/zhan-2022-impact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/zhan-2022-impact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The effects of a mismatch between thermal comfort modeling and HVAC controls from an occupancy perspective</title>
      <link>/publication/ono-2022-effects/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/ono-2022-effects/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Total Building Performance Approach to Real-time Occupant Centric Sensing and Control for Mixed Mode Ventilation in the Tropics</title>
      <link>/project/cot_mixed_mode/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/cot_mixed_mode/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This research has a total project value of S$3.75 million and is supported by
the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nrf.gov.sg&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;National Research Foundation Singapore&lt;/a&gt; under its
Cities of Tomorrow R&amp;amp;D Programme, and administered by the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www1.bca.gov.sg&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Building Construction Authority&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An open dataset for the calibration of building energy models</title>
      <link>/project/sbb_testbed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2021 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/sbb_testbed/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Building energy modeling has become more widely used for building performance assessment and building regulations compliance. The energy model of the SinBerBEST Cyber-Physical Testbed provides a straightforward &amp;ldquo;virtual testbed&amp;rdquo; platform for evaluating the performance, efficiency, and effectiveness of technological innovations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, before using for technological assessments, the testbed model itself should be calibrated using in-situ experiments from various operating conditions to ensure it reasonably follows the testbed&amp;rsquo;s real thermal and energy performance. Besides, the dataset derived from the calibration experiments will form a high-quality open empirical dataset that is rare in current model calibration research. The available datasets would be ideal as a benchmark dataset for assessing the predictive accuracy of different calibration algorithms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main objectives of this experiment are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To calibrate the SinBerBEST Testbed EnergyPlus model using in-situ experiments&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To obtain high-quality experimental datasets for building energy model validation/calibration of thermal and energy performance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;acknowledgement&#34;&gt;Acknowledgement&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This research is supported by the National Research Foundation, Prime Minister’s
Office, Singapore under its Campus for Research Excellence and Technological
Enterprise (CREATE) programme. It was funded through a grant to the Berkeley
Education Alliance for Research in Singapore (BEARS) for the Singapore-Berkeley
Building Efficiency and Sustainability in the Tropics (SinBerBEST) Program.
BEARS has been established by the University of California, Berkeley as a center
for intellectual excellence in research and education in Singapore.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A study on the transferability of computational models of building electricity load patterns across climatic zones</title>
      <link>/publication/ward-2021-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/ward-2021-study/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data requirements and performance evaluation of model predictive control in buildings: A modeling perspective</title>
      <link>/publication/zhan-2021-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/zhan-2021-data/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Occupancy data at different spatial resolutions: building energy performance and model calibration</title>
      <link>/publication/chong-2021-occupancy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/chong-2021-occupancy/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eplusr: A framework for integrating building energy simulation and data-driven analytics</title>
      <link>/publication/jia-2020-eplusr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/jia-2020-eplusr/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data science for building energy efficiency: A comprehensive text-mining driven review of scientific literature</title>
      <link>/publication/abdelrahman-2021-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/abdelrahman-2021-data/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Effects of ceiling fans on airborne transmission in an air-conditioned space</title>
      <link>/publication/li-2021-effects/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/li-2021-effects/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Occupant behavior modeling methods for resilient building design, operation and policy at urban scale: A review</title>
      <link>/publication/dong-2021-occupant/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/dong-2021-occupant/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced machine learning based control for HVAC systems</title>
      <link>/project/kajima/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/kajima/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An NUS-Kajima project funded by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kajima.com.sg/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Kajima Singapore&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SDE4 building at NUS is Singapore’s first net zero energy and WELL gold
certified building. For the NUS-Kajima collaboration project, we would like to
take it to the next level by implementing advanced machine learning based
control for the HVAC systems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reinforcement learning has been successful in applications as diverse as
autonomous helicopter flight, robot legged locomotion, playing video games,
marketing strategy selection, etc. It also has the ability to keep perfecting
its algorithm during online deployment. With such a powerful tool, we are
exploring a practical approach to integrate it into the real world building. By
optimal control of the room temperature setpoint and ceiling fan speed at the
same time, we can not only achieve a more energy efficient operation, but also
maximize the occupants’ thermal comfort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The objectives of this study are to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop a multi-objective reinforcement learning control with short-term
historical data for the hybrid cooling system in SDE4 building to minimize
the energy consumption while maximize the thermal comfort.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrate the real-world control performance in an open office or a studio
room at SDE4.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;featured.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An automated framework for model predictive control</title>
      <link>/project/mpc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/mpc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Model predictive control (MPC) has shown great potential in improving the
building operation performance and saving energy. However, its actual
implementation is restricted by the high configuration cost. Control-oriented
model is the cornerstone of MPC and the most challenging part. Due to the
paucity of a systematic understanding, it is also hard to estimate the efforts
required to obtain the model. Therefore, this study aims at improving the
scalability of MPC by addressing modeling-related issues and establishing an
automated framework.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While many past studies demonstrated the usefulness of MPC through simulation
and experiments, more attention is required for quantifiable relationships
between data requirement, model performance, and control performance. The data
used to obtain the model and implement control is essential for the ultimate
performance. However, data availability and quality vary among different
buildings. Therefore, an important question for scalability is what data is
necessary and/or desired. On the other hand, it is unclear how the predictive
capability of control-oriented models affects the control performance. The
answer to this question involves a model performance evaluation approach, which
tests not just the predictive accuracy, and series of experiments to quantify
the relationships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Virtual testbeds with single and multi-zone emulators are implemented to
address the questions. Different data availability conditions are designed to
obtain alternative control-oriented models. All alternatives are
comprehensively evaluated in terms of prediction and control performance.
Thereby, quantitative relationships between data requirement, model
performance, and control performance are established. The virtual experiments
are partially duplicated in an actual testbed for verification. Subsequently,
a MPC framework is proposed to automatically configure and evaluate the models
based on data availabilities and control purposes. The framework is showcased
in actual buildings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;featured.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Epwshiftr: an R package for creating future weather files under climate changes for building energy simulation</title>
      <link>/project/epwshiftr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/epwshiftr/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;A free, open-source R package called &amp;lsquo;epwshiftr&amp;rsquo; for adapting EnergyPlus
Weather (EPW) files to incorporate climate change predictions using the
morphing method. The focus of this package is to automatically process big
amounts of climate change model data from the latest CMIP6 GCMs and create
future EPW files for world-wide locations in a user-friendly and flexible way.
It is capable of processing multiple GCM outputs at various spatial and
temporal resolutions. The package is designed into a modularity style. Each
module stores data in a standard data format, which allows to explore
a considerably broad pool of ready-to-use methods available in R for customized
statistical analysis. Most computational-intensive processes have been designed
to run in parallel for speed-up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;acknowledgement&#34;&gt;Acknowledgement&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This research is supported by the National Research Foundation, Prime Minister’s
Office, Singapore under its Campus for Research Excellence and Technological
Enterprise (CREATE) programme. It was funded through a grant to the Berkeley
Education Alliance for Research in Singapore (BEARS) for the Singapore-Berkeley
Building Efficiency and Sustainability in the Tropics (SinBerBEST) Program.
BEARS has been established by the University of California, Berkeley as a center
for intellectual excellence in research and education in Singapore.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life cycle cost optimization</title>
      <link>/project/lcc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/lcc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Life-cycle cost analyses (LCCA) is usually coupled with whole building energy
optimization to generate the cost-optimal design with good energy efficiency.
Comparing with the isolated building system optimization, a combination of
passive and active strategies is generally recognized that can result in a lower
life-cycle cost (LCC) with better energy performance in the literature. With the
passive design parameters being optimized, the heating and cooling load of the
building could be decreased, leading to a reduction in the size of the HVAC
system. for integrated building design. However, in the current cost-optimal
decision-making framework, there is no difference in the costing process whether
it is performed on the integrated building system or the single system energy
optimization. Although the dynamic energy simulation can well demonstrate the
energy benefit gained from the integrated design, the cost-benefit usually be
highly underestimated due to the little considering of the effect that load
reductions have on the capital and running costs of the HVAC system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Against this background, this research proposes a holistic LCC optimization
approach for the integrated building design, which concerns the cost integration
between passive design and HVAC costs and the tradeoff between initial
investment for ECMs and long-term benefits. Three LCC optimization methods are
performed for the case study and their impact on Pareto front solutions’ energy
and cost performance is compared in this study. This research can contribute to
a better understanding and interpretation of the cost-effectiveness in energy
conservation, which is the basis for successful design decisions and policy
implementation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To improve energy efficiency, evaluating the energy savings potential of energy
conservation measures (ECMs) is a critical task. During new buildings design or
building retrofits, occupancy and plug-loads schedules can significantly impact
building energy use and is a leading factor in uncertainty when determining the
effectiveness of ECMs and operation strategies. Current simulation-based
assessment methods simplify the occupancy related schedules by using a standard
or representative set of static and homogeneous assumptions. The simplification
contributes to significant gaps between the simulated and measured actual energy
performance of buildings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This study presents a framework for identifying and quantifying the impact of
occupancy-related schedules on ECMs’ performance using building energy
simulation. An institutional building located in Singapore is used for a case
study. Two spatial resolution and five temporal resolution are combined to
establish different base models for energy simulation, representing different
accuracy levels of occupancy-related schedules. Then, a simulation workflow is
performed for each ECM to determine its energy savings under different levels of
input schedules. Finally, the ECM decision is determined based on the simulated
energy performance and compared among different base models. This research can
contribute to our understanding of the interactions between model complexity and
energy efficiency design, facilitating future discussions on the right level of
abstraction when modeling occupancy in building performance simulation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;featured.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eplusr: A framework for integrating building energy simulation and data-driven analytics</title>
      <link>/project/eplusr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/eplusr/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Building energy simulation (BES) offers an alternative approach that encourages
customized, integrated design solutions, and the development of BES tools has
been pronounced over the decades. The core tools are the whole-building
energy simulation programs that provide users with key building performance
indicators such as energy use and demand, temperature, humidity, and costs.
However, BES, with an iterative nature inside, can produce a large amount of
data. The volumes of the data have overwhelmed traditional data analysis
methods such as spreadsheets and ad-hoc queries with a large number of factors
to be considered. Solutions in most existing software and applications have
limited post-processing capacities on BES results. They are not flexible enough
to enable a clear understanding and control of how the data is being
transformed. There is a need to improve the efficacy and integration between
data-driven analytics and BES, and efforts should be made to develop integrated
tools that are capable of leveraging both methods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As BES becomes more integral to many aspects of architecture design and
decision-making processes, computational reproducibility has become
increasingly important to researchers, designers and practitioners. Lack of
credibility in BES results due to a lack of reproducibility is widely
considered a problem by the energy modeling community. Issues in simulation
reproducibility are mainly caused by the absence of (1) an integrated workflow
between BES and data-driven analytics and (2) a portable and reusable
computational environment encapsulating essential software and applications to
perform it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To address these issues, this paper introduces a new framework for integrating
BES and data-driven analytics. The framework is different from existing ones
because of its data-centric design philosophy. The objectives are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;to provide better and more seamless integration between BES engine EnergyPlus
and R-programming data-driven analytics environment through a parametric
simulation prototype with structured inputs and outputs format.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;to build infrastructures for portable and reusable BES computational
environment to facilitate reproducibility research in building energy
domain.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To achieve seamless integration between BES and data-driven analytics, we
propose a framework consisting of the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I/O processors for structuring BES inputs and outputs for seamless
integration with data analytics workflow.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A parametric prototype for conducting flexible and extensible parametric
simulations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A computational environment that is based on Docker containerization
to facilitate reproducibility research in the energy
simulation domain.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;featured.png&#34; width=&#34;50%&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first two components have been packaged into a free, open-source R package
&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/hongyuanjia/eplusr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;eplusr&lt;/a&gt; which is
distributed using &lt;a href=&#34;https://cran.r-project.org/package=eplusr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;CRAN&lt;/a&gt; (The
Comprehensive R Archive Network). The third component has been encapsulated
using Docker containerization and is distributed using &lt;a href=&#34;https://hub.docker.com/r/hongyuanjia/eplusr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Docker
Hub&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;get-started-with-eplusr&#34;&gt;Get Started with &lt;em&gt;eplusr&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The source code is hosted on &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/hongyuanjia/eplusr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;.
The R package can be easily installed using:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-r&#34;&gt;install.packages(&amp;quot;eplusr&amp;quot;)
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Below shows some feature highlights of the eplusr package:&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;view_geometry.gif&#34; alt=&#34;View IDF geometry in 3D&#34; width=&#34;50%&#34; /&gt;



&lt;figcaption data-pre=&#34;Figure &#34; data-post=&#34;:&#34; &gt;
  
  &lt;p&gt;
    View IDF geometry in 3D
    
    
    
  &lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;autocomplete.gif&#34; alt=&#34;Turn RStudio into a model editor via autocompletion&#34; width=&#34;50%&#34; /&gt;



&lt;figcaption data-pre=&#34;Figure &#34; data-post=&#34;:&#34; &gt;
  
  &lt;p&gt;
    Turn RStudio into a model editor via autocompletion
    
    
    
  &lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;epw.gif&#34; alt=&#34;Query and modify weather file&#34; width=&#34;50%&#34; /&gt;



&lt;figcaption data-pre=&#34;Figure &#34; data-post=&#34;:&#34; &gt;
  
  &lt;p&gt;
    Query and modify weather file
    
    
    
  &lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;job.gif&#34; alt=&#34;Query output via SQL in Tidy format which is much better for data analysis&#34; width=&#34;50%&#34; /&gt;



&lt;figcaption data-pre=&#34;Figure &#34; data-post=&#34;:&#34; &gt;
  
  &lt;p&gt;
    Query output via SQL in Tidy format which is much better for data analysis
    
    
    
  &lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;param.gif&#34; alt=&#34;Flexible and extensible parametric simulation interface&#34; width=&#34;50%&#34; /&gt;



&lt;figcaption data-pre=&#34;Figure &#34; data-post=&#34;:&#34; &gt;
  
  &lt;p&gt;
    Flexible and extensible parametric simulation interface
    
    
    
  &lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;vignettes&#34;&gt;Vignettes&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please see these vignettes and articles about {eplusr}&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://hongyuanjia.github.io/eplusr/articles/eplusr.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Introduction to eplusr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://hongyuanjia.github.io/eplusr/articles/job.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Run simulation and data exploration&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://hongyuanjia.github.io/eplusr/articles/param.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Parametric simulations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://hongyuanjia.github.io/eplusr/articles/transition.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Update IDF version&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://hongyuanjia.github.io/eplusr/articles/epw.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Work with weather files&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://hongyuanjia.github.io/eplusr/articles/schedule.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Work with Schedule:Compact objects&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://hongyuanjia.github.io/eplusr/articles/geom.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Work with geometries&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://hongyuanjia.github.io/eplusr/articles/faq.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Frequently asked questions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;slides&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://hongyuanjia.github.io/eplusrIntro/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Slides: Interfacing EnergyPlus using R&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;additional-resources&#34;&gt;Additional resources&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;eplusr manual: &lt;a href=&#34;https://hongyuanjia.github.io/eplusr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;https://hongyuanjia.github.io/eplusr/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;eplusr Docker image: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/hongyuanjia/eplusr-docker&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;https://github.com/hongyuanjia/eplusr-docker&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://cran.r-project.org/package=epwshiftr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;epwshiftr&lt;/a&gt; for creating future
EnergyPlus weather files using CMIP6 data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/hongyuanjia/epluspar&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;epluspar&lt;/a&gt; for conducting parametric
analysis on EnergyPlus models, including sensitivity analysis, Bayesian
calibration and optimization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;acknowledgement&#34;&gt;Acknowledgement&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This research is supported by the National Research Foundation, Prime Minister’s
Office, Singapore under its Campus for Research Excellence and Technological
Enterprise (CREATE) programme. It was funded through a grant to the Berkeley
Education Alliance for Research in Singapore (BEARS) for the Singapore-Berkeley
Building Efficiency and Sustainability in the Tropics (SinBerBEST) Program.
BEARS has been established by the University of California, Berkeley as a center
for intellectual excellence in research and education in Singapore.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building categorization revisited: A clustering-based approach to using smart meter data for building energy benchmarking</title>
      <link>/publication/zhan-2020-building/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/zhan-2020-building/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A framework for the continuous Bayesian calibration of building energy models</title>
      <link>/publication/chong-2019-continuous/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2019 17:47:28 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/chong-2019-continuous/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A new BIM to BEM framework: The development and verification of an open-source gbXML to EnergyPlus translator for supporting building life cycle performance analysis</title>
      <link>/publication/xu-2019-gbeplus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/xu-2019-gbeplus/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A robust unsupervised framework for high-resolution building energy consumption profiling</title>
      <link>/publication/zhan-2019-robust/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/zhan-2019-robust/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Continuous-time Bayesian calibration of energy models using BIM and energy data</title>
      <link>/publication/chong-2019177/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/chong-2019177/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whole building energy model for HVAC optimal control: A practical framework based on deep reinforcement learning</title>
      <link>/publication/zhang-2019472/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/zhang-2019472/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Example Page</title>
      <link>/tutorial/example/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/example/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;In this tutorial, I&amp;rsquo;ll share my top 10 tips for getting started with Academic:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;tip-1&#34;&gt;Tip 1&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;tip-2&#34;&gt;Tip 2&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generating certified energy models in Singapore through an M&amp;V framework.</title>
      <link>/project/mv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/mv/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An NUS project in collaboration with &lt;a href=&#34;https://arch.gatech.edu/people/godfried-l-augenbroe&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Professor Godfried L. Augenbroe (Georgia
Institute of Technology)&lt;/a&gt;,
funded by NUS Start-up Grant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2009, the Building and Construction Authority (BCA) in Singapore set an
ambitious plan to have at least 80% of the buildings in Singapore be Green Mark
certified by 2030. With measures in place to meet this 80% target, the number
of Green Mark certified buildings has grown significantly from 17 during the
launch of the BCA Green Mark scheme in 2005 to more than 2100 in 2014. With the
exponential increase in the number of Green Mark certified buildings, there is
an urgent need for the verification of their actual performance. The need to
&amp;ldquo;validate performance, raise and build awareness and capability&amp;rdquo; has also been
identified as one of the key initiatives of the S\$52 Million Green Buildings
Innovation Cluster (GBIC) Fund allocated by the Singapore National Research
Foundation (NRF), in the most recent third green building masterplan released
by BCA. Currently, the best practices for M&amp;amp;V are documented in several
guidelines, including the International Performance Measurement and
Verification Protocol (IPMVP), ASHRAE Guideline 14 and M&amp;amp;V Guidelines prepared
for the U.S. Department of Energy (DOE) Federal Energy Management Program
(FEMP). Most of these efforts are driven by the need to use a BEM to predict
the savings of different Energy Conservation Measures (ECM). The benefits of
having validated BEMs of the building stock go however beyond this, as is
becoming clear in recent resilient community and energy microgrid studies etc.
This research targets the M&amp;amp;V protocols to arrive at validated BEM&amp;rsquo;s for this
multitude of future uses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The finds from this research could facilitate the creation of a web-platform
for data sharing, automated sensor to BEM mapping, automated calibration,
guided M&amp;amp;V and advanced retrofit analysis to support the concept of life-cycle
building energy modelling (BEM).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The objectives of this research project are:
1. Produce a framework for M&amp;amp;V laying guidelines with regards to data
   resolution and model fidelity.
2. Be one of the few that addresses the important problem of
   non-identifiability that is typically neglected in BEM calibration studies.
3. Provide insights into how the level of resolution of sensor data might
   influence the level of confidence in the model.
4. Demonstrate the advantages and disadvantages of using a low fidelity model
   for calibration and how it compares with a high-fidelity model.
5. Come up with a cost-benefit analysis of different methods to generate
   certified building energy models.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The outcomes will be crucially important for scaling up to the Singapore building stock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;featured.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Deep Reinforcement Learning Approach to Using Whole Building Energy Model For HVAC Optimal Control</title>
      <link>/publication/zhang-2018-deep/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/zhang-2018-deep/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green and cool roofs’ urban heat island mitigation potential in tropical climate</title>
      <link>/publication/yang-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/yang-2018/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guidelines for the Bayesian calibration of building energy models</title>
      <link>/publication/chong-2018527/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/chong-2018527/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A comparison of MCMC algorithms for the Bayesian calibration of building energy models</title>
      <link>/publication/chong-2017-comparison/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/chong-2017-comparison/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian calibration of building energy models with large datasets</title>
      <link>/publication/chong-2017343/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/chong-2017343/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Energy utilizability concept as a retrofitting solution selection criterion for buildings</title>
      <link>/publication/yang-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/yang-2017/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improving evolutionary algorithm performance for integer type multi-objective building system design optimization</title>
      <link>/publication/xu-2016714/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/xu-2016714/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Imputation of missing values in building sensor data</title>
      <link>/publication/chong-2016-missing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/chong-2016-missing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multi-objective optimization of building envelope, lighting and HVAC system designs</title>
      <link>/publication/xu-2016-multi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/xu-2016-multi/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty analysis and parameter estimation of HVAC systems in building energy models</title>
      <link>/publication/chong-2015-hvac/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/chong-2015-hvac/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty analysis in building energy simulation: A practical approach</title>
      <link>/publication/chong-2015-practical/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/chong-2015-practical/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Predicting the envelope performance of commercial office buildings in Singapore</title>
      <link>/publication/chong-201366/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/chong-201366/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Performance evaluation of misting fans in hot and humid climate</title>
      <link>/publication/wong-20102666/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/wong-20102666/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slides</title>
      <link>/slides/example/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/slides/example/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;welcome-to-slides&#34;&gt;Welcome to Slides&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Academic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;features&#34;&gt;Features&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Efficiently write slides in Markdown&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-in-1: Create, Present, and Publish your slides&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supports speaker notes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile friendly slides&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;controls&#34;&gt;Controls&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Next: &lt;code&gt;Right Arrow&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;Space&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous: &lt;code&gt;Left Arrow&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start: &lt;code&gt;Home&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finish: &lt;code&gt;End&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Overview: &lt;code&gt;Esc&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Speaker notes: &lt;code&gt;S&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fullscreen: &lt;code&gt;F&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zoom: &lt;code&gt;Alt + Click&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/hakimel/reveal.js#pdf-export&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;PDF Export&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;code&gt;E&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;code-highlighting&#34;&gt;Code Highlighting&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inline code: &lt;code&gt;variable&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Code block:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-python&#34;&gt;porridge = &amp;quot;blueberry&amp;quot;
if porridge == &amp;quot;blueberry&amp;quot;:
    print(&amp;quot;Eating...&amp;quot;)
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;math&#34;&gt;Math&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In-line math: $x + y = z$&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Block math:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$$
f\left( x \right) = \;\frac{{2\left( {x + 4} \right)\left( {x - 4} \right)}}{{\left( {x + 4} \right)\left( {x + 1} \right)}}
$$&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;fragments&#34;&gt;Fragments&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make content appear incrementally&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;{{% fragment %}} One {{% /fragment %}}
{{% fragment %}} **Two** {{% /fragment %}}
{{% fragment %}} Three {{% /fragment %}}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Press &lt;code&gt;Space&lt;/code&gt; to play!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;fragment &#34; &gt;
   One
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;fragment &#34; &gt;
   &lt;strong&gt;Two&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;fragment &#34; &gt;
   Three
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A fragment can accept two optional parameters:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;class&lt;/code&gt;: use a custom style (requires definition in custom CSS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;weight&lt;/code&gt;: sets the order in which a fragment appears&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;speaker-notes&#34;&gt;Speaker Notes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Add speaker notes to your presentation&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-markdown&#34;&gt;{{% speaker_note %}}
- Only the speaker can read these notes
- Press `S` key to view
{{% /speaker_note %}}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Press the &lt;code&gt;S&lt;/code&gt; key to view the speaker notes!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;aside class=&#34;notes&#34;&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Only the speaker can read these notes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Press &lt;code&gt;S&lt;/code&gt; key to view&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/aside&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;themes&#34;&gt;Themes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;black: Black background, white text, blue links (default)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;white: White background, black text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;league: Gray background, white text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;beige: Beige background, dark text, brown links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;sky: Blue background, thin dark text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;night: Black background, thick white text, orange links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;serif: Cappuccino background, gray text, brown links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;simple: White background, black text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;solarized: Cream-colored background, dark green text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;


&lt;section data-noprocess data-shortcode-slide
  
      
      data-background-image=&#34;/img/boards.jpg&#34;
  &gt;


&lt;h2 id=&#34;custom-slide&#34;&gt;Custom Slide&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Customize the slide style and background&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-markdown&#34;&gt;{{&amp;lt; slide background-image=&amp;quot;/img/boards.jpg&amp;quot; &amp;gt;}}
{{&amp;lt; slide background-color=&amp;quot;#0000FF&amp;quot; &amp;gt;}}
{{&amp;lt; slide class=&amp;quot;my-style&amp;quot; &amp;gt;}}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;custom-css-example&#34;&gt;Custom CSS Example&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s make headers navy colored.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Create &lt;code&gt;assets/css/reveal_custom.css&lt;/code&gt; with:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-css&#34;&gt;.reveal section h1,
.reveal section h2,
.reveal section h3 {
  color: navy;
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;questions&#34;&gt;Questions?&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://discourse.gohugo.io&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Ask&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Documentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
