<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on IDEAS Lab</title>
    <link>/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on IDEAS Lab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Total Building Performance Approach to Real-time Occupant Centric Sensing and Control for Mixed Mode Ventilation in the Tropics</title>
      <link>/project/cot_mixed_mode/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/cot_mixed_mode/</guid>
      <description>A research project with a total project value of S$3.75 million funded by the National Research Foundation Singapore under its Cities of Tomorrow R&amp;amp;D Programme, and administered by the Building Construction Authority.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An open dataset for the calibration of building energy models</title>
      <link>/project/sbb_testbed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2021 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/sbb_testbed/</guid>
      <description>Building energy modeling has become more widely used for building performance assessment and building regulations compliance. The energy model of the SinBerBEST Cyber Physical Testbed provides a straightforward “virtual testbed” platform for evaluating the performance, efficiency and effectiveness of technological innovations.
However, before using for technological assessments, the testbed model itself should be calibrated using in-situ experiments from various operation conditions to make sure it follows reasonably the real thermal and energy performance of the testbed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced machine learning based control for HVAC systems</title>
      <link>/project/kajima/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/kajima/</guid>
      <description>Advanced machine learning based control for the HVAC systems</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An automated framework for model predictive control</title>
      <link>/project/mpc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/mpc/</guid>
      <description>This study aims at improving the scalability of MPC by addressing
modeling-related issues and establishing an automated framework.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Epwshiftr: an R package for creating future weather files under climate changes for building energy simulation</title>
      <link>/project/epwshiftr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/epwshiftr/</guid>
      <description>An R package for creating future weather files under climate changes for building energy simulation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life cycle cost optimization</title>
      <link>/project/lcc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/lcc/</guid>
      <description>Life cycle cost optimization</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eplusr: A framework for integrating building energy simulation and data-driven analytics</title>
      <link>/project/eplusr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/eplusr/</guid>
      <description>A framework for seamless integration between Building Energy Simulation (BES) and data-driven analytics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generating certified energy models in Singapore through an M&amp;V framework.</title>
      <link>/project/mv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/mv/</guid>
      <description>Generating certified energy models in Singapore through an M&amp;amp;V framework.An NUS project in collaboration with Professor Godfried L. Augenbroe (Georgia Institute of Technology)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>